qvcemail.com 2012-11-04

# The QVC Privacy Statement — Customer Service — QVC.com

At QVC, we are committed to giving you quality service. As part of that commitment, we gather information about our customers, users of our websites and other services, and visitors so we can better serve you. Because we realize that your privacy is important to you, your privacy is also important to us. Whether you visit or buy from our show, one of our stores, or one of our websites such as QVC.com, or through one of our other services such as QVC's mobile services or a QVC software application (i.e., a widget) downloaded to your desktop (all of which together with our websites we will refer to as "services"), you can be assured that we respect the confidentiality of personal information that identifies you and treat that information responsibly. As described in this Privacy Statement, we do not authorize the selling or renting of your personal information to third parties for their business purposes. 

By using a QVC service, you accept the practices that are described in this Privacy Statement, which is effective as of September 11th, 2008, and is part of the General Terms and Conditions of Use governing use of this website and the terms and conditions governing any other QVC service you use. If, however, another QVC service sets forth a separate or additional privacy statement, terms and conditions, or other policy, then that separate privacy statement, terms and conditions, or other policy shall apply in connection with your use of that service. This Privacy Statement does not apply to personal information that is collected through the websites of QVC's affiliates based outside the United States or through any other services offered by QVC's affiliates outside the United States. We may change or add to this Privacy Statement from time to time. When that happens, we will post the revised Privacy Statement here. Your use of one of our services after changes to this Privacy Statement have been posted constitutes your knowledge and acceptance of those changes (i.e., that the changes may be applied to the information we collect from and about you). 

QVC is not responsible for the privacy or data collection policies or practices of the services from which you access our services, of services we link to, or of any services that are linked to our services. 

This Privacy Statement tells you what kinds of information we collect about our customers, users, and visitors, how we use that information and with whom we may share it, and how you can access and change our information about you. If you have additional questions about QVC's privacy practices or would like more information, please contact [Privacy-Statement@QVC.com](mailto:Privacy-Statement@QVC.com?nonqiclink). 

  * What personal information do we collect from our customers?
  * What other kinds of customer information do we collect?
  * How do we collect this information?
  * How do we use cookies?
  * How do we use web beacons?
  * What if you don't want to give us personal information?
  * How do we protect our customers' personal information?
  * How do we use information about our customers?
  * How do we share customers' personal information with third parties?
  * How do we share other kinds of information about our customers with third parties?
  * How can users check or change the information we collect from or about them?
  * What are third party affinity programs?
  * Do we collect personal information from children?
  * View our Safe Harbor Statement

##  What personal information do we collect from our customers? 

We gather personal information about our customers so we can better serve you, and we make reasonable efforts to ensure the security of your personal information and to treat that information responsibly. We collect the personal information that you give us voluntarily or in response to our request when you choose to purchase a product from us or use one of our services. For example, when you register with QVC we will ask you to provide information such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, and telephone number. Registration with QVC is generally required to make a purchase or to use one of our community functions such as posting a message on a community forum or submitting a product review. Similarly, we will ask you for contact information if you use our notify a friend program or if you request that we send you e-newsletters or other promotional notices or seek information or assistance from us. 

If you purchase a product, we will also ask you for financial information such as your _QCard®_ or other credit card number and for a billing address and a shipping address. 

Additional personal information may be collected from you in connection with your use of certain optional services and features we offer. For example, if you register for QVC's mobile services, we will ask you to provide information such as your cell phone number and the name of your mobile provider, as well as the payment method, billing address, and shipping address you want to use for any purchases through this service. You will also be requested to specify payment and shipping information in advance if you want to purchase items using a speed purchase feature. Similarly, entering one of our contests or sweepstakes, submitting an employment application, or using one of our community functions may involve our collection of further personal information from you such as your social security number and chosen nickname. If you sign up to receive _Today's Special Value®_ e-mails, messages or e-newsletters, you may be asked to provide information concerning your personal interests. We may also collect personal information from your creation of wish lists or reminders. 

If you are a member of one of our third party affinity programs, we may also collect personal information from you about your membership and your purchases from us. 

Return to top

##  What other kinds of customer information do we collect? 

If you ask us to ship a purchase to somebody else or you use our notify a friend feature, we will ask you to provide the name and address or e-mail address of the person to whom you are sending or recommending the product, as well as your name and contact information. 

We may also obtain personal information about you such as contact information, updated address and shipping instructions, and credit information from agents, consultants, contractors, carriers, and other third parties. We may also collect contact and other information about prospective customers. 

Additionally, our system keeps track of technical information about your computer or mobile device, such as the browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, and operating system of your computer, the Internet Service Provider (ISP) or other provider you use to access certain of our services, and your internet protocol (ip) address, location, and time zone setting. To help us understand the use of our services by our visitors and improve your shopping experience and to aid us in marketing and managing our services, we also automatically collect information as to how you were directed to them, how you navigate around them, what products you browse, and your purchasing activities. 

Return to top

##  How do we collect this information? 

When you register with QVC, we compile the personal information you give us about yourself into an individual profile, adding other personal information about you to that profile as we obtain it. We also collect information about your purchases and other uses of our services as they occur. 

Personal and other information about prospective customers may be collected by us or obtained from our business partners or other third parties. 

We automatically gather other information (including the technical information identified above) when you access certain of our services, including through the use of cookies and web beacons. 

Return to top

##  How do we use cookies? 

Cookies enhance our ability to serve you. Basically, they're pieces of text that a website stores on your computer – an identification code of sorts. This cookie can be accessed by the website when you revisit it. 

We use two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies terminate shortly after you terminate your internet session. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive until they expire or are deleted. Both types of cookies help provide an enhanced user experience since they recall your use of the Internet and our services, shopping preferences, shopping cart information, and your password. 

We understand that not everyone wants to permit the use of cookies. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies and how to disable cookies, but we recommend that you leave cookies turned on so that you can take full advantage of the shopping features we offer. 

Return to top

##  How do we use web beacons? 

Web beacons are small, transparent graphics that are placed on web pages to track how visitors arrive at a website and what they do there. We use web beacons to track customers' visits to and browsing activities at our websites and to compile sales and statistical data. For example, beacons let us know when a purchase is made on one of our websites by a member of one of our third party affinity programs and when a purchase is initiated by an advertisement we placed on a third party's website. This information assists us in marketing and managing our websites and enhancing your shopping experience. 

Return to top

##  What if you don't want to give us personal information? 

Personal information is required for you to make a purchase, request information or assistance, or take advantage of certain services and features we offer, such as QVC's mobile services and desktop applications, our notify a friend feature, community functions, contests or sweepstakes, or on-line employment applications. If you do not want to provide personal information through use of these services and features, you are free to look for products offered through any of our marketing channels and place a telephone order by calling 1.888.345.5788 toll-free or by visiting one of our stores. We respect the confidentiality of all your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement whether you give it to us over the telephone, at one of our stores, or via any other means. 

Return to top

##  How do we protect our customers' personal information? 

QVC participates in the VeriSign Secured Seal Program. All of your personal information is encrypted by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software when it is transmitted to us via the Internet to any website address beginning with https. We maintain the servers that store this information in a facility with restricted access. We also truncate your credit card number to the last four digits when we communicate with you about your order. 

Return to top

##  How do we use information about our customers? 

We use your personal information to process your orders. This includes for example, contacting you to confirm your order, fulfilling it, and shipping it. We may also contact you about your order. 

Additionally, we will use your contact information to send you e-newsletters or other promotional notices, or to respond to requests for information or assistance from you. 

If you are a member of one of our third party affinity programs, we will use and disclose your personal information to administer and manage that program. Similarly, if you choose to participate in certain services or features we offer such as QVC's mobile services and desktop applications, our notify a friend feature, community functions, contests or sweepstakes, and on-line employment applications, we will use your personal information to administer and manage those services and features. 

We may also use your personal information to improve our service to you, to customize the content you see, and for research, marketing, and other business purposes. For example, we periodically review customer information as part of servicing our accounts. We may also contact you from time to time to inform you of the services that we offer and to gather information about how we can improve them. 

Finally, we analyze information we obtain automatically, including from cookies and web beacons, concerning our customers' use of, access to, and navigation of our services and their browsing and purchasing activities to improve, customize, and market our services and content, to enhance our customers' shopping experiences, and for research, marketing, and other business purposes. 

Return to top

##  How do we share customers' personal information with third parties? 

In order to receive and process your orders and requests, we may provide your name, address, and other personal information, such as your e-mail address and telephone number, to other entities such as credit card companies and package delivery services (for example, American Express, Visa, UPS, and USPS). Similarly, if you order a product that is shipped directly from another company, or offered by us in conjunction with another company, we will share personal information about that order with the other company. 

We may use third party agents, consultants, and contractors to perform business functions on our behalf, including customer service, credit review, account servicing, customer research, marketing, provision of IT services, and records maintenance. We give these entities access to our customers' personal information to perform these functions for us. We DO NOT authorize them to use that information for any other purpose. 

Additionally, we share personal information about you when you voluntarily use certain optional services and features we offer. For example, if you are a member of one of our third party affinity programs, we will share information concerning your purchases from us with the organization running that program. If you ask us to send a particular product to another person or use our notify a friend feature, we will tell that person we are sending the product or e-mail at your request. If you participate in a contest or sweepstakes or submit an employment application, we may share the information you submit with others assisting us in the administration of that feature. If you use one of our community functions, the content of your posting will be available to all other participants and will be accompanied by your user name or chosen nickname. 

It is possible that QVC or part of its business or one of its affiliates could merge with, acquire or be acquired by another business entity and your personal information could be among the assets transferred. If this occurs, you will be notified of the change by e-mail or notice on this website or one of our other services. 

We reserve the right to share personal information about you with our affiliates in the course of our business operations. We also reserve the right to share personal information about you when we believe this to be appropriate to comply with the law or in cooperation with legal authorities, to enforce the General Terms and Conditions governing use of this website and the terms and conditions governing the use of our other services, or to protect the rights, property, safety, or other interests of QVC and its customers. 

Return to top

##  How do we share other kinds of information about our customers with third parties? 

We may share non-personal, non-individually identifiable information about our customers with the group of people with whom we share personal information, as well as with other third parties such as vendors, advertisers, and marketing firms. 

Return to top

##  How can users check or change the information we collect from or about them? 

You can always review your personal profile at QVC and correct or update it by going to the area of one of our services dealing with customers' accounts and accessing the specific type of information that you wish to correct or update. You can also change personal information such as your shipping address or payment method when ordering. 

You can subscribe to or unsubscribe from e-newsletters and other promotional notices by going to the area on one of our services dealing with customers' accounts and accessing the type of communication service you wish to change. 

Our customer service representatives are also ready to assist you in checking or changing your personal profile or removing your name from our contact lists. You can reach them through links to customer service that appear throughout our services, by e-mail, or by calling 1.888.345.5788 toll-free or writing to: 

> QVC, Inc.  
>  Customer Service  
>  1200 Wilson Drive  
>  West Chester, PA 19380 

You can opt out of our use of cookies to recall information about you by setting your browser not to accept cookies or to disable cookies. You cannot access or change the non-personal information that we collect. However, you can opt out of the process by which certain categories of information are collected at this website by clicking here. 

Return to top

##  What are third party affinity programs? 

Occasionally, we participate in rewards programs with other business organizations where customers who are also members of these businesses will get a credit or a reward for their QVC purchases from the other member organizations. We also sometimes advertise QVC products on other services in the form of a link so that visitors can click over to our services and purchase the products if they are interested. In these situations, we share information about our customers' QVC purchases with these other member organizations and other services under the contracts these entities have with QVC. 

Return to top

##  Do we collect personal information from children? 

Our services are not intended for use by children, and the terms and conditions governing the use of our services require that you must be at least 18 years old to use them. In addition, we do not solicit or collect information from anyone who tells us that he or she is under 13 years of age. 

Return to top
